{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"10.0.1","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":1500,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":11,"width":640,"height":480,"responsive":false,"scalable":true,"launchFile":"index.html"},"contentStructure":[{"id":"Text_Caption_331","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_331","title":"Information Security Awareness Quiz --The Humans of Security-- ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_574","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_574","title":"Take our Security Quiz   to test your knowledge.    Click on Begin to start. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_575","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_575","title":"Brought to you by the Information Security Branch  Office of the Chief Information Officer ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_9","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si21887","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si21901","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide21706","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_331","Text_Caption_574","Text_Caption_575","Button_9","si21887","si21901"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide21706"}}},{"id":"Image_189","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_189","roles":{}},{"id":"si12441","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_338","roles":{}},{"id":"si12349","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_327","title":"1. You receive an urgent email from your CEO requesting money to be sent to a contractor you have never heard of. The email is asking you to send a large sum of money and was sent outside of working hours. True or False?  You should transfer the money right away. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12360","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_328","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12364","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_329","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12360_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si12382","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_332","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12386","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_333","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12382_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si12435","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_337","roles":{}},{"id":"si12459","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_42","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12473","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_43","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19347","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19361","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19593","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19606","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19621","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19634","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19649","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19662","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19677","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19690","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12405","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_334","title":"Correct - Answer: False  A fraudster will impersonate a company executive faking their identity. They will do this by either gaining access to their email address or spoofing the email address and therefor spear phishing you. If you are ever asked to send large amounts of money, make sure you double check the facts with the person communicating to you.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12417","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_335","title":"Incorrect  - Answer: False  A fraudster will impersonate a company executive faking their identity. They will do this by either gaining access to their email address or spoofing the email address and therefor spear phishing you. If you are ever asked to send large amounts of money, make sure you double check the facts with the person communicating to you.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12429","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_336","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide12483","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_189","si12349","si12364","si12386","si12459","si12473","si19347","si19361","si19593","si19606","si19621","si19634","si19649","si19662","si19677","si19690","si12429"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12483"},"question":{"interactionId":"12329","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"1. You receive an urgent email from your CEO requesting money to be sent to a contractor you have never heard of. The email is asking you to send a large sum of money and was sent outside of working hours.\rTrue or False?  You should transfer the money right away.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_190","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_190","roles":{}},{"id":"si22070","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_714","roles":{}},{"id":"si21978","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_698","title":"2. On average how long does it take for organizations to detect a data breach that is due to email phishing? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21989","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_704","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21993","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_705","title":"1 min 46 seconds ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21989_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_394","roles":{"answer":{"title":"1 min 46 seconds\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22000","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_706","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22004","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_707","title":"1 hour and 46 minutes ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22000_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_395","roles":{"answer":{"title":"1 hour and 46 minutes\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24737","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24741","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"46 hours ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24737_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"46 hours\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24752","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24756","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"146 days ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24752_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"146 days\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si22064","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_713","roles":{}},{"id":"si22092","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_103","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22110","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_104","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22132","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_105","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22150","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_106","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22162","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22174","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22186","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22198","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22210","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22222","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22234","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22246","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22034","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_710","title":"Correct - Answer:  D  The answer is 146 days!  Yes, it takes close to an average of five months before organizations become wise to phishing attacks. In that amount of time, attackers would have been able to get everything in your network, or in the victim's computers. In fact, social engineering has overtaken malware as the preferred attack method in a data breach. Only three percent of attacks involve malware, while 97 percent use social engineering.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22046","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_711","title":"Incorrect - Answer:  D  The answer is 146 days!  Yes, it takes close to an average of five months before organizations become wise to phishing attacks. In that amount of time, attackers would have been able to get everything in your network, or in the victim's computers. In fact, social engineering has overtaken malware as the preferred attack method in a data breach. Only three percent of attacks involve malware, while 97 percent use social engineering.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22058","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_712","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide22259","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_190","si21978","si21993","si22004","si24741","si24756","si22092","si22110","si22132","si22150","si22162","si22174","si22186","si22198","si22210","si22222","si22234","si22246","si22058"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide22259"},"question":{"interactionId":"21958","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"2. On average how long does it take for organizations to detect a data breach that is due to email phishing?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_191","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_191","roles":{}},{"id":"si22393","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_725","roles":{}},{"id":"si22301","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_699","title":"3. What are the top emotional motivators that social engineers use on humans when phishing? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22312","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_715","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22316","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_716","title":"Fear, Curiosity, recognition and entertainment ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22312_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_397","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Fear, Curiosity, recognition and entertainment\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22323","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_717","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22327","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_718","title":"Entertainment, social, reward and recognition ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22323_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_398","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Entertainment, social, reward and recognition\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si22334","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_719","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22338","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_720","title":"Curiosity, reward, social and recognition ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22334_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"399","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Curiosity, reward, social and recognition\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24815","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24819","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Reward, fear, entertainment and social  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24815_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Reward, fear, entertainment and social \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22387","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_724","roles":{}},{"id":"si22415","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_107","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22433","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_108","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22455","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_109","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22473","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_110","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22485","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22497","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22509","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22521","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22533","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22545","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22557","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22569","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22357","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_721","title":"Correct - Answer: B  As more companies adopt preventative measures, the older motivators like fear and curiosity have caused fewer successful phishing scams. This means that 'consumer scams' targeting employees personally while on the job have increased in frequency. The lines can become blurry when employees are using personal devices for work or checking their social or news notifications whilst taking a break.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22369","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_722","title":"Incorrect  - Answer: B  As more companies adopt preventative measures, the older motivators like fear and curiosity have caused fewer successful phishing scams. This means that 'consumer scams' targeting employees personally while on the job have increased in frequency. The lines can become blurry when employees are using personal devices for work or checking their social or news notifications whilst taking a break.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22381","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_723","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide22582","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_191","si22301","si22316","si22327","si22338","si24819","si22415","si22433","si22455","si22473","si22485","si22497","si22509","si22521","si22533","si22545","si22557","si22569","si22381"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide22582"},"question":{"interactionId":"22281","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"3. What are the top emotional motivators that social engineers use on humans when phishing?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_192","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_192","roles":{}},{"id":"si22716","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_736","roles":{}},{"id":"si22624","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_700","title":"4. How many unfilled Cyber Security jobs are expected by 2021? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22635","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_726","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22639","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_727","title":"10, 000 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22635_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"10, 000\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22646","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_728","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22650","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_729","title":"100, 000 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22646_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"100, 000\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si22657","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_730","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22661","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_731","title":"1 Million ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22657_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"1 Million\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22928","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22932","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"3.5 Million ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22928_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"3.5 Million\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si22710","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_735","roles":{}},{"id":"si22738","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_111","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22756","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_112","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22778","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_113","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22796","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_114","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22808","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22820","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22832","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22844","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22856","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22868","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22880","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22892","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22680","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_732","title":"Correct - Answer: D   It is predicted that by 2021 the unfilled cybersecurity jobs worldwide will reach 3.5 million. Currently more than 300,000 cybersecurity jobs in the U.S. are unfilled, and postings are up 74% over the past five years.  Humans of Cyber Security, we need you!  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22692","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_733","title":"Incorrect  - Answer: D  It is predicted that by 2021 the unfilled cybersecurity jobs worldwide will reach 3.5 million. Currently more than 300,000 cybersecurity jobs in the U.S. are unfilled, and postings are up 74% over the past five years.  Humans of Cyber Security, we need you!  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22704","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_734","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide22905","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_192","si22624","si22639","si22650","si22661","si22932","si22738","si22756","si22778","si22796","si22808","si22820","si22832","si22844","si22856","si22868","si22880","si22892","si22704"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide22905"},"question":{"interactionId":"22604","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"4. How many unfilled Cyber Security jobs are expected by 2021?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_193","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_193","roles":{}},{"id":"si23144","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_749","roles":{}},{"id":"si23041","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_701","title":"5.  What is the main target of cyber criminals? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23052","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_737","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23056","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_738","title":"Company networks ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23052_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_403","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Company networks\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23063","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_739","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23067","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_740","title":"Targeted corporation executives ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23063_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_404","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Targeted corporation executives\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23074","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_741","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23078","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_742","title":"Large retail corporations ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23074_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"399_405","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Large retail corporations\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23085","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_743","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23089","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_744","title":"Internet users ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23085_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"406","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Internet users\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si23138","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_748","roles":{}},{"id":"si23166","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_115","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23184","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_116","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23206","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_117","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23224","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_118","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23236","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23248","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23260","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23272","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23284","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23296","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23308","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23320","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23108","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_745","title":"Correct - Answer:  D  Due to the large number of internet users, the ‘human attack surface’ has moved ahead of machines as the top target for cyber crime.  There were nearly 3.9 billion internet users in 2018 (51% of the world population).  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23120","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_746","title":"Incorrect  - Answer:  D  Due to the large number of internet users, the ‘human attack surface’ has moved ahead of machines as the top target for cyber crime.  There were nearly 3.9 billion internet users in 2018 (51% of the world population).  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23132","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_747","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide23333","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_193","si23041","si23056","si23067","si23078","si23089","si23166","si23184","si23206","si23224","si23236","si23248","si23260","si23272","si23284","si23296","si23308","si23320","si23132"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide23333"},"question":{"interactionId":"23021","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"5.  What is the main target of cyber criminals?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_194","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_194","roles":{}},{"id":"si23482","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_763","roles":{}},{"id":"si23379","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_750","title":"6.  The ‘Grandma Scam’ is where someone claiming to be a grandchild contacts a senior citizen in desperate need of money.  How much are senior citizens robbed of each year by scams like these? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23390","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_751","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23394","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_752","title":"Approximately $500 Million ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23390_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_407","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Approximately $500 Million\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23401","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_753","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23405","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_754","title":"Roughly $7.5 Million ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23401_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_408","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Roughly $7.5 Million\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24779","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24783","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Eighty million dollars ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24779_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Eighty million dollars\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24794","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24798","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Estimated $3 Billion ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24794_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Estimated $3 Billion\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si23476","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_762","roles":{}},{"id":"si23504","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_119","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23522","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_120","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23544","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_121","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23562","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_122","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23574","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23586","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23598","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23610","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23622","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23634","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23646","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23658","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23446","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_759","title":"Correct - Answer:  D  Sadly, it is estimated that 3 billion dollars are stolen from senior citizens each year in scams.  AARP explains that even well-educated seniors (doctors and lawyers) have fallen prey to this scam as it reaches them on an emotional level.  Discuss scams like this with senior citizens you may know, particularly those within your family.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23458","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_760","title":"Incorrect  - Answer:  D  Sadly, it is estimated that 3 billion dollars are stolen from senior citizens each year in scams.  AARP explains that even well-educated seniors (doctors and lawyers) have fallen prey to this scam as it reaches them on an emotional level.  Discuss scams like this with senior citizens you may know, particularly those within your family.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23470","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_761","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide23671","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_194","si23379","si23394","si23405","si24783","si24798","si23504","si23522","si23544","si23562","si23574","si23586","si23598","si23610","si23622","si23634","si23646","si23658","si23470"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide23671"},"question":{"interactionId":"23359","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"6.  The ‘Grandma Scam’ is where someone claiming to be a grandchild contacts a senior citizen in desperate need of money.  How much are senior citizens robbed of each year by scams like these?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_195","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_195","roles":{}},{"id":"si23820","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_777","roles":{}},{"id":"si23717","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_764","title":"7.  The most susceptible age group for online scams and financial fraud is? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23728","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_765","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23732","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_766","title":"Millennials ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23728_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_411","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Millennials\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si23739","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_767","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23743","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_768","title":"Under 15 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23739_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_412","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Under 15\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23750","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_769","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23754","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_770","title":"Senior Citizens ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23750_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"399_413","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Senior Citizens\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24830","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24834","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Ages 35 - 55 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24830_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Ages 35 - 55\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23814","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_776","roles":{}},{"id":"si23842","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_123","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23860","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_124","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23882","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_125","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23900","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_126","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23912","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23924","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23936","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23948","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23960","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23972","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23984","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23996","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23784","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_773","title":"Correct - Answer: A  Surprised?  When you think about it, millennials are the group that spend more of their time online, whether gaming, surfing the web, looking at YouTube or texting.  The average affluent person in the 18 – 34 year old age group spends approximately 53 hours per week online and are prolific users of social media.  Seniors, however, tend to lose more money per each loss than millennials.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23796","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_774","title":"Incorrect  -  Answer: A  Surprised?  When you think about it, millennials are the group that spend more of their time online, whether gaming, surfing the web, looking at YouTube or texting.  The average affluent person in the 18 – 34 year old age group spends approximately 53 hours per week online and are prolific users of social media.  Seniors, however, tend to lose more money per each loss than millennials.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23808","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_775","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide24009","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_195","si23717","si23732","si23743","si23754","si24834","si23842","si23860","si23882","si23900","si23912","si23924","si23936","si23948","si23960","si23972","si23984","si23996","si23808"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide24009"},"question":{"interactionId":"23697","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"7.  The most susceptible age group for online scams and financial fraud is?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_196","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_196","roles":{}},{"id":"si24158","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_791","roles":{}},{"id":"si24055","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_778","title":"8. What percent of Malware is targeted at humans? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24066","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_779","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24070","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_780","title":"45% ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24066_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_415","roles":{"answer":{"title":"45%\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24077","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_781","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24081","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_782","title":"78% ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24077_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_416","roles":{"answer":{"title":"78%\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24845","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24849","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"89% ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24845_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"89%\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24860","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24864","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"97% ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24860_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"97%\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si24152","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_790","roles":{}},{"id":"si24180","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_127","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24347q7","for":"Slide24347q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24198","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_128","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide24347q7","for":"Slide24347q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24220","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_129","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24347q7","for":"Slide24347q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24238","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_130","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24347q7","for":"Slide24347q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24250","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24347q7","for":"Slide24347q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24262","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24347q7","for":"Slide24347q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24274","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide24347q7","for":"Slide24347q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24286","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide24347q7","for":"Slide24347q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24298","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24347q7","for":"Slide24347q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24310","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24347q7","for":"Slide24347q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24322","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24347q7","for":"Slide24347q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24334","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24347q7","for":"Slide24347q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24122","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_787","title":"Correct - Answer: D  only about 3% of malware tries to exploit an exclusively technical flaw. The other 97% target instead users through Social Engineering. Hacking attempts increasingly focus on the human vulnerabilities of an information elaboration system instead of lapses in software or hardware.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24134","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_788","title":"Incorrect  - Answer: D  only about 3% of malware tries to exploit an exclusively technical flaw. The other 97% target instead users through Social Engineering. Hacking attempts increasingly focus on the human vulnerabilities of an information elaboration system instead of lapses in software or hardware.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24146","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_789","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide24347","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_196","si24055","si24070","si24081","si24849","si24864","si24180","si24198","si24220","si24238","si24250","si24262","si24274","si24286","si24298","si24310","si24322","si24334","si24146"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide24347"},"question":{"interactionId":"24035","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"8. What percent of Malware is targeted at humans?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_185","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_185","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_107","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_107","title":"Quiz Results ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6059","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6083","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6091","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6055","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You Scored: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6079","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Total Questions: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6087","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Accuracy: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6103","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6107","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6121","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20489","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20502","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20517","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20530","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6038","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6038"}}},{"id":"si6231","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_186","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_186","roles":{}},{"id":"Button_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_4","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19054","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19068","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_9","title":" Stay Current With Information Security By Subscribing to the:   Weekly Security News Digest ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_298","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_298","title":"Thank you for taking the quiz.  To exit the quiz, close the browser window. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6219","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si6231","Image_186","Button_4","si19054","si19068","SmartShape_9","Text_Caption_298"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":600},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6219"}}},{"id":"Pool502","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":502,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"Nov2019Quiz","class":"project","title":"Nov2019Quiz","children":["Slide21706","Slide12483","Slide22259","Slide22582","Slide22905","Slide23333","Slide23671","Slide24009","Slide24347","Slide6038","Slide6219"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":458,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":["Slide12483q0","Slide22259q1","Slide22582q2","Slide22905q3","Slide23333q4","Slide23671q5","Slide24009q6","Slide24347q7"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":80,"passScore":64}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"quiz","CCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"SCCriteria":"quiz","SCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide21706","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide12483","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide22259","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide22582","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide22905","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide23333","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide23671","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide24009","title":"Slide 8"},{"id":"Slide24347","title":"Slide 9"},{"id":"Slide6038","title":"Slide 10"},{"id":"Slide6219","title":"Slide 11"}]}